[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the herb dandelion mean in French?", "correct_answer": "Lions tooth", "incorrect_answers": ["Lions head", "Lions mane", "Lions heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the famous movie, Casablanca, Ugarte is arrested at Ricks Cafe, but manages to escape.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these behaviors is typical of ant societies?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Ability to solve complicated problems", "Communication between individuals", "Division of labor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Grease, directed by Randal Kleiser, takes place in what year?", "correct_answer": "1959", "incorrect_answers": ["1950", "1954", "1956"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, is Rosies dad in Costa Luna?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This filmmaker, famous for directing Runaway Train and Tango  Cash, is the brother of Academy Award-winning director Nikita Mikhalkov.", "correct_answer": "Andrey Konchalovsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Roman Polanski", "Andrei Tarkovsky", "Sergei Mikhalkov"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first written reference of Blackjack can be found in a short story by this world-famous author.", "correct_answer": "Miguel de Cervantes", "incorrect_answers": ["Hans Christian Anderson", "Mark Twain", "Victor Hugo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who may use the .gov domain?", "correct_answer": "US federal agencies", "incorrect_answers": ["Governments of any country (payment goes to UN funds)", "Governors of US states", "Governments of any country (free)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How often does Halleys comet appear?", "correct_answer": "Every 76 years", "incorrect_answers": ["Every 100 years", "Every 30 years", "Every 25 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog, who first showed up in a Bud Light Beer Super Bowl ad, had a black circle around one eye.", "correct_answer": "Spuds MacKenzie", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue MacKenzie", "Long John", "Spottie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Asian country did the recipe for the Miso soup originate?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "China", "Thailand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lauren Hutton, who starred in the movie Malone, played Fiona McNeil in two episodes of Nip/Tuck.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]